



Лебедев Алексей

Male, 26 years, born on 28 June 1995

+375 (29) 5663608 — WhatsApp/Telegram

71pixels@gmail.com — preferred means of communication

Skype: Mymashell@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lebedev-alexey/

Reside in: Minsk

Citizenship: Belarus, work permit at: Belarus Ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

IT Project Manager | Web Development & Game Dev | Scrum Master

Specializations:

Project manager
 Employment: full time
 Work schedule: full day

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 7 years 9 months

January 2018 — till now 4 years 6 months

lolsurprise.by

Belarus, lolsurprise.by/

Product Director | Retail

Online shop of branded children's toys. My own small business in Minsk, Belarus.

- Made by me from scratch
- 80+ SKU
- More than 5000 orders in 4.5 years
- 50+ regular customers
- Stable supply chains
- Wholesale deliveries to other countries

January 2022 — June 2022 6 months

7tam

Tbilisi, 7tam.net

IT, System Integration, Internet

• Software Development

IT Project Manager | Game Dev

Cross-platform games for iOS & Android devices.

- Working closely with the founder about new ideas and finding new insights
- Setting up an Agile Scrum methodology for a more effective time tracking system
- Confluence documentation
- Competitive analysis and market research
- Trendwatching
- Roadmapping
- Managing developer's team
- Working with invoices

- Managing 2 games development process
- Managing 2+ outsource projects

November 2019
— February 2022
2 years 4 months

Motorrika

Moscow, motoring.ru/

IT Product Manager | Web Development

Internal react application for pilots and administrators of the Russian Championship of road moto racing | appmotoring.com

- Special product for a specific business
- Setting up an Agile Scrum methodology in JIRA Atlassian Software for a more effective time tracking system
- Confluence documentation
- Made from scratch by my developer's team in accordance with technical and functional requirements
- Competitive analysis and market research
- An online shop of motorcycle tires is inside the application
- Ability to expand functionality by using new technologies
- 250+ pilots are using the application and enjoying

The main website of the Russian Championship of road moto racing | motoring.ru

- Design of the site and branding
- Support

June 2016 — April 2019 2 years 11 months

Upwork

Freelance Sales & Project Manager | Web Development and Services

Worked in sales and management. 30+ clients in fintech, crypto, medicine, logistics (cargo), and gaming.

- Own remote team of 9 developers
- 70+ projects completed in accordance with technical and functional requirements
- Implementation of JIRA Atlassian products for clients with fixed-price contracts

April 2015 — July 2016 1 year 4 months

Мобильные ТелеСистемы (МТС), Беларусь

Minsk, www.mts.by

Telecommunications, Communications

• Mobile Communications

Sales Manager | Retail

Sales specialist in the online store.

- Highest performance in the sales department
- 8+ sold products is an average per day
- Mentored 5+ people in the company

December 2012

— May 2013
6 months

Мобильные ТелеСистемы (МТС), Беларусь

Minsk, www.mts.by

Telecommunications, Communications

• Mobile Communications

Sales Manager | Retail

Sales specialist in the online store.

- Highest performance in the sales department
- 8+ sold products is an average per day
- Mentored 5+ people in the company

Education

Master

2022 Международный университет "МИТСО", Минск

Логистики, Логистика

Белорусский государственный экономический университет,

Минск

Финансов и банковского дела, Финансы

Electronic certificates

2022

EFSET English Certificate 61/100 (C1 Advanced)

Key skills

Languages

Belarusian — Native

English — B2 — Upper Intermediate

Russian — C2 — Proficiency

Skills

Веб-аналитика

Ведение переговоров

Управление проектами

Организаторские навыки

Управление продажами

Развитие продаж

Agile Project Management

Scrum

Atlassian Jira

Проектный менеджмент

Менеджмент Atlassian Confluence

Driving experience

Own car

Driver's license category B

Further information

7tam

Recommendations

Stanislav (Founder)

About me

Hello everyone! My name is Alexey. I'm from Minsk, Belarus (UTC+3)

I'm glad to share some facts about me and my professional skills. So I'm 27 years old. Born in Belarus, Minsk. Now I'm living in Tbilisi because there are a lot of my friends and colleagues here. It's a pretty good country for living, working remotely, and traveling. Highly recommend and invite you! But I can return to Belarus if it's necessary.

About my goals and professional skills.

I've been working with people since 2012 and really like to provide the best service for my customers. I started with sales, then I continue my career freelance, and then (2018) I decided to create my own small retail business. The business helped me to combine and improve all of my

skills - sales, management, economics, logistics, marketing, and web development. It's a successful online store of branding toys that still works.

During one of my business trips to Moscow, I was noticed by the organizers of the Russian Road Racing Championship. Since then, I have worked with my developer's team on the creation and maintenance of all Championship web resources.

So I would be happy to help your team with my rich experience. Looking for new opportunities!

Activities.

Very like swimming, skiing, hiking and walking on foot, sometimes we are going to play football with friends. So if you are in Tbilisi and like sports activities too, feel free to write me:)